Love doesn't always arrive on schedule.
Lucky 7 is a romance, comedy, tv movie film directed by Harry Winer.
Instead of really living her life since losing her mother at age 7, Seattle lawyer Amy Myer sticks to a
foolproof 'timeline' her mother drew as a guideline to help plot the course of her life.
The timeline, which proves to be accurate in all other respects,
predicts that Amy should marry her seventh boyfriend.
However, Amy must question her instincts when she feels that her sixth
boyfriend is the one she should marry, not the predicted seventh.
Now she must decide whether to follow her mother's
advice, or follow her own heart.
Amy Myer, played by Kimberly Williams-Paisley.
Peter Connor, played by Patrick Dempsey.
Daniel McCandless, played by Brad Rowe.
Bernie Myer, played by Brian Markinson.
Ray, played by Lochlyn Munro.
Maya, played by Michelle Harrison.
Lucky 7 is a 2003 American television film starring
Patrick Dempsey and Kimberly Williams.
The film premiered on ABC Family on July 20, 2003.
In the film, a female lawyer arranges her life according
to the predictions of her deceased mother.
Her mother predicted that she would marry her 7th boyfriend, but the lawyer is
confused when she concurrently dates two boyfriends following a break-up.
Which one is the 6th boyfriend and which one the
7th boyfriend is unclear to her.
The film explores themes of businessman, fireworks,
seattle, washington, road trip, lawyer.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.